Guide to the Student Association records, 1935-2005 RG0023
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Student Association files, 1992-2016; RG0023 Series 7; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 1, Box 5, Box 4)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Alternative Calendar Update, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Housing Analysis, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Undergraduate Admissions, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-February 28, 2003, Attended Minutes-October 18, 2002, 15 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Pocket Matter, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Athletics and Recreation, Parent Services, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS Communication and Technology/ RESNET, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Marvin Center and Student Activities Center, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association Report, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: University Police Department, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: The Alternative Academic Calendar Study Group, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Court Ruling and Its Impact on Campus Housing, Lottery and Management, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Financial Assistance, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Undergraduate Admissions, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-October 18, 2002, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Matter, 28 February 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS Comm/Technological Update, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Athletics Update, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Alumni Relations Update, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Associate VP and Dean of Students Updates, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Activities Updates, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Financial Assistance Update, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association Report, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Admissions Report, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-February 7, 2002, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Committee Charge, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Matter, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Pocket Matter, 16 May 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS Related Materials, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Other Business, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: The University Club, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Colonials Weekend 2002, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Mount Vernon Campus, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Admissions Update, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-October 18, 2001, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Pocket Matter, 7 February 2002; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 8 February 2001; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association Report, 8 February 2001; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Housing Update, 8 February 2001; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: GW World Community Program, 8 February 2001; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Admissions Update, 8 February 2001; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-October 19, 2000 Meeting, 8 February 2001; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Matter, 8 February 2001; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Parents' Association Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: University Police Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Activities Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Communications and Technology Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Athletics Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Housing Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Financial Aid Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Admissions Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association Update, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Strategic Planning for Mount Vernon College Campus, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Matter, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Pocket Matter, 19 October 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Report from Executive Session to the Board of Trustees, February 11, 2000, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Community Service Update, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: "Sweatshop" issues, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Ongoing Student Initiatives, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Safety and Security Report- IMF/World Bank Review, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Parents' Association Update, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Housing Update, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Financial Aid Update, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Admissions Update, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association Resolution and Historical Documents, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Matter, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Pocket Matter, 18 May 2000; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Senate Meeting # 8 through Senate Meeting #9-Documents [1/3], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Senate Meeting # 8 through Senate Meeting #9-Rules, 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Senate Meeting # 8 through Senate Meeting #9-Documents [2/3], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meeting # 8 through Senate Meeting #9-Documents [3/3], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Senate Elect #1 through Senate Meeting #4 and Committee Documents [1/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Senate Elect #1 through Senate Meeting #4 and Committee Documents [2/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Senate Elect #1 through Senate Meeting #4 and Committee Documents [3/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Senate Elect #1 through Senate Meeting #4 and Committee Documents [4/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Files '98-'99 #1: Senate Elect General, Events, Newsletter and Public Relations, Rules Committee, Academic Affairs Committee, 1998-1999; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Files '98-'99 #1: Finance Committee and Student Life Committee, 1998-1999; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Files '98-'99 #1: Parliamentary Procedure Issues, Meeting Logistics and Secretary Information, GW Votes!, 1998-1999; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Finance Committee 2012-2013 Binder of Record: Governing Documents and Legislation, Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Finance Committee 2012-2013 Binder of Record: Minutes and Finance Records, Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Finance Committee 2012-2013 Binder of Record: Proposals/Initiatives, Fee Incentive, Notes/Papers, Other, Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Files 1998-1999 #2-Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, Tuition Action Director, Community Issues, Mount Vernon Campus Issues, and University, Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Files 1998-1999 #2: Finance Reform, Constitution Revision Committee, D.C. College Consortium, Dining Services Commission and Marvin Center Governing Board Transition, Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Files 1998-1999 #: hatchet and Miscellaneous, Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Governing Board 1972-1973 Documents [1/3], Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Governing Board 1972-1973 Documents [2/3], Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Governing Board 1972-1973 Documents [3/3], Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board Minutes 1973-1974 [1/3], Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board Minutes 1973-1974 [2/3], Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board Minutes 1973-1974 [3/3], Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda, 15 January 1987; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Documents, 1987-1988; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Documents, January 1988; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Financial Documnets, March 1988; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Documents, January 1989; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees #3, 16 March 1989; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda, 20 October 1988; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Documents, 1984-1985; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate, 30 April 2009; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes, 10 April 2009; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Gift Acceptance Policy, 12 October 2007; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Decision Memorandum, Undated; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 2001; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bill, 2007; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Inauguration of Dr. Steven Knapp, 13-16 November 2007; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - MCGB [Marvin Center Governing Board] Ad-hoc Committee on Renovation 91995-1996)-notes, proposals and cover letters, 1995-19961; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Student Organization Resource Center-Planning and Implementation, 1996; Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - MCGB [Marvin Center Governing Board] Newsletter (1996-1997), Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1997 Excellence in Student Life, Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Credit Union News (1996-1997), Series 7 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Marvin Center Information, Posting Policies, Student Activities Center, Student Organizations, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - University Policies, Money Manual, Planning Process, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Space and Scheduling, Leadership Tips, Frequently Used Forms, and Financial Process Manual, 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Attendance Rosters, 1969-1970; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Agenda and Minutes [1/3], 1970; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Agenda and Minutes [2/3], 1969-1970; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Agenda and Minutes [3/3], 1970; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Constitutions, 1969; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Agreements for Use of Student Office Space, 2008; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board Student Organization Documents [1/2], 2007-2010; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board Student Organization Documents [2/2], 2007-2010; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Fifth Floor Marketing Report, 28 April 1998; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Student Dining and Recreation Survey, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Marvin Center Marketing Research, 1997; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Expert Choice, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bowling, 1998; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - About MCGB [Marvin Center Governing Board], 2004; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Student Organization Space Basics: Application, Criteria, 1998; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Office Allocations, 2004; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Excellence of MCGB [Marvin Center Governing Board], 1997; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Copies of Meeting Minutes 1997-1998, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Senate Special Meeting #3: Back Pocket Matter, 1 February 2005; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Senate Special Meeting #3: Binder Material, 1 February 2005; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Senate Special Meeting #3: Front Pocket Matter, 1 February 2005; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - President's Journal 2007: Student Meetings, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - President's Journal 2007: Knapp/Chernak, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - President's Journal 2007: Other, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - President's Journal 2007: Division Leaders, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - President's Journal 2007: VPS, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - President's Journal 2007: Tim Miller, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - President's Journal 2007: Front Matter, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - President's Journal 2007: Front Pocket Matter, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Back Pocket Matter, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Department of Athletic Update, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Communication and Creative Services Update, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Student Association Update, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Association Vice President and Dean of Freshmen Update, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Assistant Vice President, SASS Department Updates, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Associate Vice President and Dean of Students Department Updates, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: University Police Department Update, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: GW Housing Programs Update, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: SASS Strategic Initiatives Update, Guide to Personal Sucess Program, Customer Service Initiatives, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Student Financial Assistance Update, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Undergraduate AdmissionsUpdate, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Fair and Accurate Credit Transactions Act (FACTA), Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Student and Academic Support Services Annual Report, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: May 15, 2008 Meeting Minutes, 15 May 2008; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Meeting from Student and Faculty Community: Agenda, Charge, and Meeting Planner, Undated; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Fall 2013 Audit, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Fall 2013 Allocations, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014:Balance Sheet Detail 6/30/13, 30 June 2013; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Balance Sheet Detail 3/28/14 (3)-Unbrellas, March 28, 2014; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Balance Sheet Detail 3/28/14 (2)-Administration, March 28, 2014; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Balance Sheet Detail 3/28/14 (1) Program, March 28, 2014; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Front Matter, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Balance Sheet Detail 6/30/13, June 30, 2013; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Balance Sheet Detail 3/28/14 (2), March 28, 2014; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Balance Sheet Detail 3/28/14, March 28, 2014; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Front Matter, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - SA Finance Committee Records 2012-2014: Front Pocket Matter, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-Back Pocket Matter, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-Student Association Report, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-Appointment with Tenure Recommendations, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-Emeritus Status Recommendations, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-Honorary Degree Nomination, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002- 19 October 2000 Meeting Minutes, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-PhD in Counseling, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-Master of International Studies, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-College of Professional Studies- GW Learning Solutions, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Unmarked-Academic Affairs Committee 2000-2002-Front Pocket Matter, Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Vice President for Academic Affairs, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Student Association, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Faculty Senate, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Minutes, 18 May 2000 Meeting, May 18, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Appointment with Tenure Recommendations, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Emeritus Status Recommendations, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Honorary Degree Nominations, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Grievances Procedures, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: College of Professional Studies, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - 19 October 2000 Copy: Front Pocket Matter, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - 19 October 2000: Vice President for Academic Affairs, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - 19 October 2000: Student Association, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - 19 October 2000: Faculty Senate, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - 19 October 2000: Minutes, 18 May 2000 Meeting, May 18, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - 19 October 2000: Appointment with Tenure Recommendations, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - 19 October 2000: Emeritus Status Recommendations, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - 19 October 2000: Honorary Degree Nominations, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - 19 October 2000: Grievances Procedures, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - 19 October 2000: College of Professional Studies, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - 19 October 2000: Front Pocket Matter, October 19, 2000; Series 7 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Employee Manual circa 1992, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1997 Tuition Increase, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - MC [Marvin Center] Emergency Procedures and Security 1997-1998, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SORC [Student Organization Resource Center], 1996-1997; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - RHA [Residence Hall Association], 1997-1998; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Student Activities Center 1997-1998, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1998 Appointment Application, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Development, November 18, 1997; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Student Leadership Conference 1996-1997, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - MC [Marvin Center] Housekeeping 1997-1998, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Business Affairs Issues: One Card, Construction, Vending 1997-1998, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Radio Station 1997-1998, Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Student Association Senate, Academic Affairs Committee 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pcard Procurement Card Policy and Procedures Handbook 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Stated Meeting of the Board of Trustees Regular Session, 2007-10-19 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Communication Division Spring 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Business Card Catalog (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Senate-Elect Meeting #1, April 6, 2004, 2004-04-06 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Office Assistant Notebook (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Report to the Faculty Assembly, Lilien F. Robinson, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Senate Legislative Binder, Fall 2002, Eric R. Daleo, Executive Vice President (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Senate Legislative Binder, Spring 2003, Eric R. Daleo, Executive Vice President (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2002-03 Senate Elect, Eric R. Daleo, Executive Vice President-Elect, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - SA Annual Report 2001-2002, Joshua Singer Executive Vice President, Binder 1 of 2, Bills and Resolutions (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Alternative Academic Calendar Committee, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - GW Board of Trustees Committee on Academic Affairs, 2001-05-17 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of President Trachtenberg with SA Student Presidents, 1991-2007 (Box 15, Folder 1-17)
- Student government records, 1935-2005; RG0023 Series 8; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)